Guide to the Time Inc. Video Group Records 1934-1989 MS 3009-RG 41
New-York Historical Society
- Series VI. Home Box Office Records, 1972-1987; 5.425 Linear feet in 8 record cartons and 1 flat box
  - Subseries VI.C. Advertising and Sales Training Materials, 1972-1984; 1.15 Linear feet in 3 record carton and 1 flat box
    - Sales Presentation and Press Kit, undated (Offsite-box 3354, Folder 4)
    - Sales Representative's Question and Answer Workbook, 1978 (Offsite-box 3354, Folder 5)
    - Sales Representative Training Manual, 1978 (Offsite-box 3354, Folder 6-7)
    - Sales Training Cassettes, undated (Offsite-box 3354, Folder 8)
      6 audiocassette: analog; 2 7/8 x 2 1/8 in. On label: "HBO Sell-A-Customer Field Sales Training Program".
    - Telephone Sales Program Guidebook, 1976 (Offsite-box 3354, Folder 9)
- Series VII.A Time-Life Films: Television Division Records, 1939-1985; 20.55 Linear feet in 22 record cartons
  Historical Note
  Time-Life Films was incorporated by Time Inc. in 1958. While the company was created at that time, Time-Life Films doesn't become a fully subsidiary of Time Inc. until December 1969 when Time-Life Films purchases the Peter M. Robeck and Company. Peter Robeck, the former owner of Peter M. Robeck and Company, is appointed as the managing director of Time-Life Films. This new subsidiary handles the sales of distribution of films within the United States with a focus on distributing materials created by the British Broadcasting Company (BBC).
  At the time that Time-Life Films purchased Peter M. Robeck and Company, it began working on television productions. Initially, these television productions were considered to part of the non-theatric division of the subsidiary. While Time-Life Films had divisions internally, the different sections of the organization weren't listed in department head lists until 1974. Internally, Time-Life Films names its divisions education, video, and non-theatric divisions but on department head lists the divisions are production, marketing, and business affairs. The divisions named on the department head lists appear to have been administrative in nature and to have overseen the work done by the internal division. The department head lists do not begin to reflect the group's internal organization until 1978 when the Television Division is listed for the first time.
  Over the course of Time-Life Films existence, the Television Division had a variety of names. Between 1972 and 1974, the division is called the Non-Theatric Division then, partially through 1974, the name is changed to the Television Division. This name is kept until at least November 1978 when the name changes to the Television Distribution Division. This name is in use until 1981 when the Television Division is reinstated. After 1982, Time-Life Films appears sporadically in department head lists.
  Time Warner Inc.: Companies and Subsidiaries. Time Inc. Reference Files (MS 3009-RG 3), New-York Historical Society.
  Time-Life Films. Time Inc. Subject Files (MS 3009-RG 1), New-York Historical Society.
  The Time-Life Films: Television Records cover the period of 1939 to 1985 with the bulk of the materials covering the period of 1973 to 1982. Materials dated prior to 1970 are mainly photocopies of materials used for research. The focus of the materials in this series is on the production of television projects and on the financial relationship that existed between Time-Life Films and the companies that they were creating co-productions with.
  The Time-Life Films: Television Division Records are arranged into six subseries:
  Subseries VII.A.1. Vice President of Promotion and Publicity Harvey Chertock Files
  Subseries VII.A.2. Public Television Production and Promotion Files
  Subseries VII.A.3. Music Cue Sheet Files
  Subseries VII.A.4. BBC Co-Production Files
  Subseries VII.A.5. Co-Production Report Files
  Subseries VII.A.6. G.I. Diary Series Files
  - Subseries VII.A.1. Vice President of Promotion and Publicity Harvey Chertok Files, 1974-1980; 1.62 Linear feet in 4 records cartons
    Harvey Chertok is first listed in Time Inc. department head lists in 1978 as the director of promotion and publicity with the Television Division of Time-Life Films. In 1979, Chertok becomes of the vice president of promotion and publicity with the television distribution division of Time-Life Films. He remains in this position until 1980. After 1980, Chertok no longer appears in department head lists.
    The Vice President of Promotion and Publicity Harvey Chertok Files cover the period of 1974 to 1980 and focus on efforts to promote the Time-Life Films television productions. The production named in this subseries are Blind Ambition, the works of Shakespeare, Ten Who Dared, and Wild, Wild World of Animals. Included in this subseries are broadcasting schedules, flyers, notes, lists of books in series and areas released, brochures, clippings, blank Wild World of Animals versus competition forms, press releases, TV Guide issues, program cue sheets, music cue sheets, episode summaries, slides, transparencies, photographs, magazine issues, press tour lists, press kits, and correspondence. The correspondence discuss sales brochures, advertising and promotional materials, promotional programs, Nielsen ratings, viewer demographics, broadcast schedules, production orders, advertising and promotion campaigns, prints, reviews, promotional trailers, screenings, and interviews.
    - Blind Ambition, 1978-1979, undated (Offsite-box 3354, Folder 10-14)
    - Blind Ambition [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Blind Ambition: Advertising, 1979 (Offsite-box 3354, Folder 15)
    - Blind Ambition: L.A. Preview and Any Special Screenings, 1979 (Offsite-box 3357, Folder 1)
    - Blind Ambition: Legal, 1979 (Offsite-box 3357, Folder 2)
    - Blind Ambition: News Releases, 1979 (Offsite-box 3357, Folder 3)
    - Blind Ambition: Publicity Clips, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 3357, Folder 4-7)
    - Blind Ambition: Reviews, 1979 (Offsite-box 3357, Folder 8)
    - Shakespeare, The Complete Works: Photographs, 1979 (Offsite-box 3357, Folder 9)
    - Ten Who Dared: Time-Life Color Photos, 1978-1980, undated (Offsite-box 3357, Folder 10-11)
    - Wild Wild World of Animals, 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 3357, Folder 12-16)
    - Wild Wild World of Animals: Promotion Kit, 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 3357, Folder 17)
    - Wild Wild World of Animals: Promotion Kit Materials, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3357, Folder 18)
    - Wild Wild World of Animals: Promotion Trailers, 1977 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 1)
    - Wild Wild World of Animals: Publicity, 1974 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 2)
    - Wild Wild World of Animals: Reviews, 1975 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 3)
  - Subseries VII.A.2. Public Television Production and Promotion Files, 1973-1982; 3.6 Linear feet in 5 records cartons
    The Public Television Production and Promotion Files cover the period of 1973 to 1982 and contain a variety of materials related to public television programs that the Television Division of Time-Life Films was involved with producing, promoting, and distributing in the United States. It is unclear who created and used these files since a number of different names appear on documents. Some of the most common names found in these files were Micheal Garin, Peter Hansen, Mary Miller, Rick Schilling, Bill Miller, Haidee Granger, Clare Simpson, Sarah Frank, and Rosemarie DiSapio. At the time that these files were created, Garin appears to have been the vice president and general manager of syndicated and public television. The others worked on public television projects. Included in this subseries are production schedules, project pitches, grant proposals, reports on technology standards, Shakespeare task force reports, invoices, clippings, comments on casting, show summaries, production notes, show introductions, market analysis reports, contracts and agreements, notes, materials and activity reports, list of support activities, project updates, study materials proposals, committee meeting transcripts, Q and A forms, floppy disks, project overview statements, assets and liabilities statements, project flow charts, cross-collaterization analysis, reports on British Broadcast Corporation (BBC) and Time-Life Films relationships, trip preparation lists, budget analysis, projected budget, production cost sheet, scripts, and correspondence. The correspondence discuss deliveries, multimedia, status reports, trips, requests for information, project updates, exhibits, broadcasts, travel, contract changes, use rights, agreements, dubbing, recording, distribution, production, technology/equipment, finances, co-productions, authorization, and acquisitions.
    - BBC: Co-Productions Binder, 1981 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 4)
    - BBC: Co-Productions: Cross-Collateralization, 1974, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 5)
    - BBC: Co-Productions: Cross-Collaterialization [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R57)
    - BBC: Co-Productions: Floppy Discs, undated (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 6)
      1 computer disc (floppy disk): 8 in., on label: "0002N Time Inc.".
      1 computer disc (floppy disk): 8 in., on label: "0004N Time Inc. continued".
    - BBC Corporation: Lionheart, 1982 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 7)
    - BBC Productions, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 8)
    - Borgias: Scripts: Episodes 1 and 3-10, undated (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 9-15)
    - Connections, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 16)
    - Making of Mankind: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 17)
    - Masterpiece Theatre, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 18-20)
    - Masterpiece Theatre [RESTRICTED], 1975-1980 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Masterpiece Theatre: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 3355, Folder 21)
    - Masterpiece Theatre: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 1)
    - Masterpiece Theatre: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1974-1977 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Mobil [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 2-3)
    - Mobil Oil Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Once Upon a Classic, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 4-6)
    - Once Upon a Classic: Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 7-8)
    - Once Upon A Classic: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Once Upon a Classic: The Talisman, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 9)
    - Pandora Films, 1980 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 10)
    - Pastoral Symphony, 1979 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 11)
    - The Prince Regent: General Correspondence and Telex's, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 12)
    - Search for Alexander: Budgets, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 13)
    - Search for Alexander: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 14)
    - Search for Alexander: Correspondence: Hallmark, 1980 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 15)
    - Search for Alexander: Correspondence: Scripts, 1980 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 16)
    - Search for Alexander: Episode Overviews, Cast Bios, and Voice Over Scripts, 1979 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 17)
    - Search for Alexander: Exhibition, 1980 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 18)
    - Search for Alexander: File No. 2 and 3, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 19-21)
    - Search for Alexander: File No. 3 [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Search for Alexander: Market by Market Analysis, 1981 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 22)
    - Search for Alexander: Mobil Oil, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 23)
    - Search for Alexander: Music Cue Sheets, undated (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 24)
    - Search for Alexander: Panel Meetings, 1978 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 25)
    - Search for Alexander: Photos, 1980 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 26)
    - Search for Alexander: Promotion, Press, and Publicity, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 27-28)
    - Search for Alexander: Press and Publicity, 1981 (Offsite-box 3356, Folder 29)
    - Search for Alexander: Press and Publicity, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 1)
    - Search for Alexander: Press Information, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 2-3)
    - Search for Alexander: Production Costs, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 4)
    - Search for Alexander: Production, Location, and Shoot Schedule, 1980 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 5)
    - Search for Alexander: Ratings, 1981 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 6)
    - Search for Alexander: Schedules, 1981 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 7)
    - Search for Alexander: Scripts: Part I-IV, undated (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 8)
    - Search for Alexander: Slide Presentation Narration, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 9)
    - Shakespeare, 1980 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 10)
    - Shakespeare: Articles, 1978 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 11)
    - Shakespeare: Books, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 12)
    - Shakespeare: Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 13-16)
    - Shakespeare: Drama and Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 17)
    - Shakespeare: Further Education, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 18)
    - Shakespeare: Plays, 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 3358, Folder 19)
    - Shakespeare: Press Conference, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 1)
    - Shakespeare: Telex's, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 2-4)
    - Shakespeare Quarterly, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 5)
    - Soul of a Nation: Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 6)
    - Soul of a Nation: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Soul of a Nation: Program License Agreement and Relative Correspondence, 1980 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 7)
    - Soul of a Nation: Program License Agreement and Relative Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Telex: Incoming: 1980 October - 1981 December, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 8-10)
    - Telex: Outgoing, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 11-13)
    - Ten Who Dared, 1977-1981 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 14)
    - Ten Who Dared [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Tomb of the Lost King: Telex's, General Correspondence, Program Agreement, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 15)
    - Tomb of the Last Kings: Telex's, General Correspondence, Program Agreement [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R57)
    - The Voyage of Charles Darwin: Agreement and General Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 16)
    - The Voyage of Charles Darwin: Agreements and General Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R57)
  - Subseries VII.A.3. Music Cue Sheet Files, 1969-1980; 1.82 Linear feet in 4 records cartons
    The Music Cue Sheet Files cover the period of 1969 to 1980. Included in this subseries are music cue sheets, program cue sheets, and reel format sheet for televisions shows that Time-Life Films was involved in producing and distributing. Additionally, there are limited amounts of correspondence discussing the use of music and music cue sheets.
    - Abdication, 1976 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 17)
    - The Africans, undated (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 18)
    - All Creature Great and Small, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 19)
    - The Ambassadors, 1977 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 20)
    - America, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 21)
    - America: Syndicated Version, undated (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 22)
    - Americans, 1978 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 23)
    - Anna Karenina, 1980 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 24)
    - Ascent of Man, undated (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 25)
    - Believers (Formerly Anno Domini), 1977 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 26)
    - Billion Dollar Bubble, 1976 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 27)
    - Billy Smart's Children's Circus, 1971-1974 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 28)
    - Black Tulip, 1970 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 29)
    - Blind Eye to Murder, 1978 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 30)
    - Bruno Walter, 1972 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 31)
    - Bull's Eye War, 1976 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 32)
    - Chicago Conspiracy Trial, 1970 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 33)
    - Civilization, 1969 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 34)
    - The Commanders, 1972 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 35)
    - Connections, 1978 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 37)
    - Crime and Punishment, 1979 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 38)
    - Dad's Army, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 39)
    - Danny Wilson After-School Special, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 40)
    - Dave Allen at Large, 1972, 1979 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 41)
    - Deep Cold War, 1977 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 42)
    - The Devil's Crown, 1978 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 43)
    - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, 1980 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 44)
    - Dr. Who, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 45-46)
    - Dr. Who: Series 4, undated (Offsite-box 3359, Folder 47)
    - Dr. Who: Series 4, 1978 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 1)
    - Duchess of Duke Street, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 2)
    - Elizabeth R, 1972 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 3)
    - Fall of Eagles, 1974 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 4)
    - Family Classics: Co-Productions, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 5)
    - Fawlty Towers, 1975 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 6)
    - Fight Against Slavery, 1975 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 7)
    - The First Churchills, undated (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 8)
    - Glittering Prizes, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 9)
    - Good Neighbors (The Good Life), 1977 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 10)
    - The Goodies, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 11)
    - Harold LLoyd, undated (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 12)
    - A Horseman Riding By, 1979 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 13)
    - Indira Ghandi, 1971 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 14)
    - Ivanhoe, 1970 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 15)
    - John Halifax Gentleman and Secret Garden, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 16)
    - K.G.B.: The Soviet Secret Police, 1974 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 17)
    - Khrushchev Remembers, undated (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 18)
    - Last of the Mohicans, 1971 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 19)
    - Leo Sayer, 1977 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 20)
    - Life Around Us, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 21)
    - Little Women, 1970 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 22)
    - The Long Search, 1977 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 23)
    - Lord Peter Wimsey, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 24)
    - Lorna Doone, 1976 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 25)
    - Magic of Dance, 1979 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 26)
    - Making of the President, undated (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 27)
    - Making of the President [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R57)
    - Malice Aforethought, 1979 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 28)
    - Marie Curie, 1977 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 29)
    - Mayor of Casterbridge, 1978 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 30)
    - Merchant of Venice, 1972 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 31)
    - The Mighty Continent, 1975 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1980 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 33)
    - Modern Arts Package, 1970 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 34)
    - Mom, the Wolfman and Me, 1980 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 35)
    - Monty Python's Flying Circus, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 36)
    - Morecambe and Wise, 1970-1977 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 37)
    - Nicholas Nicholby, 1977 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 38)
    - On Giant's Shoulders, 1979 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 39)
    - One Man's China, 1976 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 40)
    - Onedin Line, 1972 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 41)
    - Orestein, 1979 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 42)
    - Other People, Other Places, undated (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 43)
    - Other People, Other Places [RESTRICTED], 1972
    - Other People, Other Places II, 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 44)
    - The Pallisers, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 45)
    - Penmarric, 1979 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 46)
    - Pinocchio, 1978 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 47)
    - Plain Murder, 1978 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 48)
    - Pride and Prejudice, 1980 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 49)
    - Prince and the Pauper, 1976 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 50)
    - The Real McCoys, 1979 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 51)
    - Rebecca, 1979 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 52)
    - Ripping Yarns, 1977 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 53)
    - Robin Hood [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 54)
    - Search for the Nile, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 55)
    - Shakespeare, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 56)
    - Shirley Bassey Show, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 57)
    - Six Wives of Henry VIII, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 58)
    - Target, 1980 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 59)
    - Taste for Adventure, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 60)
    - Ten Who Dared (The Explorer), undated (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 61)
    - A Third Testament, undated (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 62)
    - To The Manor Born, 1979 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 63)
    - Tom Brown's School Days, 1974 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 64)
    - Tomorrow's Saudi Arabia, 1975 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 65)
    - Vision On, 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 66)
    - Voyage of Charles Darwin, 1978 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 67)
    - War and Peace, 1973 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 68)
    - Wild, Wild World of Animals I, undated (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 69-70)
    - Wild, Wild World of Animals II, 1970-1974 (Offsite-box 3360, Folder 71)
    - Wild, Wild World of Animals III, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 1)
    - Wild, Wild World of Animals IV, 1977 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 2)
    - Wild, Wild World of Animals V, undated (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 3)
    - Window on the World I and II, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 4)
    - Wodehouse Playhouse, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 5)
    - Wonderful World of Sport, undated (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 6-7)
    - World War II: G.I. Diary, undated (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 8)
    - Wuthering Heights, 1978 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 9)
    - Yesterday's Witness, 1975 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 10)
  - Subseries VII.A.4. BBC Co-Production Files, 1970-1981; 0.4 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    The BBC Co-Production Files cover the period of 1970 to 1981 and focus on production work done by Time-Life Films staff when working on British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) co-productions. Included in this subseries are copies of A Viewer's Guide to the Voyage of Charles Darwin, copies of The Search for Man program guides, promotional pamphlets for Time-Life Television The Search for Alexander the Great, status reports, project updates, summaries of BBC co-production finances, cue sheets, notes, list of programs, program scripts, meeting agendas, invoices, clippings, scripts, and correspondence. The correspondence discusses status reports, art galleries, agreements, Time-Life Television's role in production, prior use of titles, Federal Communications Commission (FCC) rules, and use of pictures.
    - Arts Feature: All the World's A Stage, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 11-12)
    - The Borgias, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Conspiracy Trial: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 14)
    - Connections (Formerly Changes), 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 15)
    - Connections: Courses by Newspaper, 1977-1979 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 16)
    - Connections: Outline Treatment and Shooting Scripts, 1977 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 17)
    - Nancy Astor (Drama Department - 1979), 1978-1979, undated (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 18-19)
    - Search for Alexander the Great: Program, 1980 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 20)
    - Search for Man: Program Guide, undated (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 21)
    - Status Reports, 1977-1981 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 22)
    - Voyage of Charles Darwin: Viewer's Guide, 1980 (Offsite-box 3361, Folder 23)
  - Subseries VII.A.5. Co-Production Report Files, 1974-1985; 1.7 Linear feet in 3 record cartons